<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Colton Fitzgerald</title>
    <description>I&#39;m a Web Developer based out of Las Vegas, NV. I build responsive, modern websites that fit today&#39;s needs.
</description>
    <link>https://coltonfitzgerald.me/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://coltonfitzgerald.me/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 18:50:31 -0800</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2015 18:50:31 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Starting the Year Off Right</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Alright, so it’s that time of the year again where everyone declares “goals” that last a week or two. This year, I thought I’d give a couple tips / apps that could help out with your hopefully sucsessful goals. Here’s a couple of my favorite things that help me work:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;keep-your-tasks-organized&quot;&gt;#1 Keep your tasks organized&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;wunderlist-free---linkhttpwunderlistcom&quot;&gt;Wunderlist (&lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt;) - &lt;a href=&quot;http://wunderlist.com&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is so important, I literally can’t even ;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One of the best ways you can keep your tasks organized is with a &lt;strong&gt;Task Manager App&lt;/strong&gt;. I prefer &lt;a href=&quot;http://wunderlist.com&quot;&gt;Wunderlist&lt;/a&gt; (Free) because it syncs well between all of my devices and other people can be added extremely easily.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;https://coltonfitzgerald.me/img/posts/subtasks@2x.png&quot; alt=&quot;Wunderlist Sub-tasks&quot; width=&quot;355&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;rescue-time-free---linkhttprescuetimecom&quot;&gt;Rescue Time (&lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt;) - &lt;a href=&quot;http://rescuetime.com&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is less of a utility that I use everyday and more of a weekly checkup. To use Rescuetime, all you have to do is run the application in the background and it will keep track of how much time you spend doing what. At the end of the week, it will send you an email letting you know how productive you were. It is a lot better than it sounds and I seriously reccomend checking it out before you make your final decision on this app.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;alfred-free---linkhttpwwwalfredappcom&quot;&gt;Alfred (&lt;em&gt;free&lt;/em&gt;) - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.alfredapp.com&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This app is amazing. It takes the already awesome Spotlight app and turns it into a powerhouse. You gain the ability to search your computer and launch apps EXTREMELY fast. If you pay for the premium version, you can hook up custom searches for anything. My favorite implementation of that is w/ Dash, so you can search documentation for any language by just typing something like: &lt;code&gt;_css margin_&lt;/code&gt; to view all the information you would ever want for the margin attribute.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;bartender-15---linkhttpwwwmacbartendercom&quot;&gt;Bartender (&lt;em&gt;$15&lt;/em&gt;) - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.macbartender.com&quot;&gt;link&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just buy it. There are no excuses for this one.&lt;br /&gt;
It adds an icon to your menu bar so that you can organize all of your menu bar items. For only $15, you really have no excuse to get this.&lt;br /&gt;
(&lt;em&gt;PS: There is a 15 day free trial&lt;/em&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy new year everyone! I hope these couple of apps help you out and feel free to comment below if any of them work / don’t work for you :)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2015 18:50:01 -0800</pubDate>
        <link>https://coltonfitzgerald.me/blog/2015/01/01/starting-the-year-off-right.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://coltonfitzgerald.me/blog/2015/01/01/starting-the-year-off-right.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>blog</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
